## **Sultan Kautsar**

Web system administrator and developer with more than three years of effective experience. Has experience with Rayatiga, individual agency specializing in building sleek, fast, modern, and responsive website with WordPress. Currently working at Breef Studio and on the fly at Rayatiga, agency.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Breef Studio,** Yogyakarta — Web Developer

May 2023 - Present

Breef Studio — PT Breef Digital Indonesia is a software development company committed to delivering the best end product possible. Providing the team to create software solutions with customer-centered innovation, design, web and software development..

## Rayatiga, Magelang — Founder & System Administrator

March 2020 - Present (OTF)

Rayatiga is an agency engaged in the field of information technology. Providing web services such as domain name reservation, WordPress, and also provides building sleek, responsive, fast also modern website. Domain at rayatiga.com.

## **Pawonkos799,** Magelang — Web System Administrator

June 2022 - April 2023

Business in Food Wholesaler, providing for frozen food and dry food. Registered copyright (HKI) by **Sultan Kautsar** at Indonesian DJKI. See the document.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Telkom University,** Bandung — *Bachelor of Information Technology*

August 2019 - February 2023

Superior study program at Telkom University focusing on the IT Support, IoT, Cyber Security, and Engineering. Graduated with **Cum Laude GPA 3.73**.

## Bangkit Academy, Jakarta — Cloud Computing Cohort

February 2022 - July 2022

Bangkit is a career readiness program that aims to produce high-caliber technical talent for world-class Indonesian technology companies and startups, fully supported by Google, GoTo, and Traveloka. Graduated with **Disctiction**.

### **PROJECT & CERTIFICATE**

## **Portfolio Website** — Projects and Achievement Page

See list of more than 10+ projects and list of more than 30+ achievements and certification at personal website, sultankautsar.com.

Rayatiga, 24 Menur Ave., Pahlawan St., Central Magelang, Magelang, 56117, Indonesia. (+62) 812-2545-9071 contact@sultankautsar.com sultankautsar.com linkedin.com/in/sultankautsar

#### **SKILL**

Web Administrator

IT Technical Support

WordPress Developer

Digital Business Development

Linux Operations (Desktop and Server)

Cloud Computing Operations (Google Cloud, AWS, and similar)

#### **ACCOMPLISHMENT**

**Telkom University Graduated with Cum Laude** majoring in
Bachelor of Information
Technology with **GPA 3.73**.

Distinction Graduate & Top 53
Product Based Capstone
Project at Bangkit Academy: by
Google, GoTo, and Traveloka

IT Support and Google Cloud Professional Certificate obtained from Coursera Specialization.

**EPrT Score 478** Internal English Test in Telkom University LaC.

**25+ Qwiklabs Badge** in Google Cloud Skills Boost.

**1,300+ Git Contributions** in a Year for committing in GitHub.

#### LANGUAGE

Indonesian (Native)
English (Intermediate, Score: 478)